[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "Do you look for appearance or personality in a mate?",
        "answers": ["Looks", "Mind"]
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "Have you been told your romantic standards were too high?",
        "answers": ["Yes", "Not that I recall"]
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "Do you get bored easily?",
        "answers": ["No", "Sure"]
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "Ever been told you have poor taste in partners?",
        "answers": ["No", "Yeah"]
      },
      {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "Are you more of a Sadist or a Masochist?",
        "answers": ["Masochist", "Sadist"]
      },
      {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "Have you changed your personal style for someone else?",
        "answers": ["Nope", "Sure"]
      },
      {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "Have you ever cheated before?",
        "answers": ["I plead the 5th", "I don't think so"]
      },
      {
        "id":8,
        "question": "Do you spend money on fads?",
        "answers": ["Yeah", "Nope"]
      },
      {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "Is age just a number?",
        "answers": ["There are limits", "It's all about love"]
      },
      {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "How do you make decisions?",
        "answers": ["My gut", "My mind"]
      },
      {
        "id": 12,
        "question": "Will you fight dirty to win at anything?",
        "answers": ["Of course", "That's not truly winning"]
      },
      {
        "id": 13,
        "question": "How does a life of no responsibility sound?",
        "answers": ["Sign me up", "No way"]
      },
      {
        "id": 14,
        "question": "Do you like children?",
        "answers": ["Love 'em", "Ugh!"]
      },
      {
        "id": 15,
        "question": "Is good housekeeping important in a partner?",
        "answers": ["Yes", "Not really"]
      },
      {
        "id": 16,
        "question": "Would you want your children to be like you?",
        "answers": ["As much as possible", "One of me is enough"]
      },
      {
        "id": 17,
        "question": "What's your take on praying mantis mating habits?",
        "answers": ["It makes me nauseous", "Whatever"]
      },
      {
        "id": 18,
        "question": "Have you ever been told you were stingy?",
        "answers": ["Maybe...", "No"]
      },
      {
        "id": 19,
        "question": "Your lover's into baby play. What do you do?",
        "answers": ["I'll try anything once", "That's a dealbreaker"]
      },
      {
        "id": 20,
        "question": "Have you ever asked a lover for forgiveness?",
        "answers": ["Yeah, so?", "No"]
      },
      {
        "id": 21,
        "question": "If you get a call from someone you don't like, do you...",
        "answers": ["Answer it", "Straight to voicemail!"]
      },
      {
        "id": 22,
        "question": "What if your lover is a good friend with someone of your sex?",
        "answers": ["I'd be bothered", "I wouldn't care"]
      },
      {
        "id": 23,
        "question": "What do you do if you doubt your lover?",
        "answers": ["Reaffirm my trust", "Talk to them"]
      },
      {
        "id": 24,
        "question": "Would you try to steal your friend's lover?",
        "answers": ["Can't stop the heart", "I'll hold back"]
      },
      {
        "id": 25,
        "question": "Is it okay to lie if you'll never be caught?",
        "answers": ["No problem there", "I still can't lie"]
      },
      {
        "id": 26,
        "question": "Someone's hitting on your lover!",
        "answers": ["Step in and end it", "Trust your lover"]
      },
      {
        "id": 27,
        "question": "Which is harder: lying or being lied to?",
        "answers": ["Lying", "Being lied to"]
      },
      {
        "id": 29,
        "question": "Your lover is cheating on you. Do you...?",
        "answers": ["Break up with them", "Make them end it"]
      },
      {
        "id": 30,
        "question": "Could you show everything in your inbox to your lover?",
        "answers": ["Of course!", "Eh...I don't think so"]
      },
      {
        "id": 32,
        "question": "Do you gesticulate while on the phone?",
        "answers": ["Who doesn't?", "That's stupid"]
      },
      {
        "id": 33,
        "question": "You've suddenly changed sexes. Where do you go?",
        "answers": ["The hospital", "The shower room"]
      },
      {
        "id": 35,
        "question": "If you were suddenly rich, would you tell your lover?",
        "answers": ["Yes, of course", "No, it's all mine"]
      },
      {
        "id": 37,
        "question": "Do you buy too much food when you're hungry?",
        "answers": ["No", "Yes"]
      },
      {
        "id": 38,
        "question": "You must kiss one of these. Choose!",
        "answers": ["A cephalopod-like alien", "A beautiful corpse"]
      },
      {
        "id": 39,
        "question": "Has being embarrassed ever turned you on?",
        "answers": ["...Yes", "No!"]
      },
      {
        "id": 40,
        "question": "Would you rather have a detailed plan or go with the flow on a spontaneous date?",
        "answers": ["Plan it out", "Spontaneity rules"]
      },
      {
        "id": 41,
        "question": "How do you feel about discussing 'safe fun' with a new partner?",
        "answers": ["Open and honest", "Keep it mysterious"]
      },
      {
        "id": 42,
        "question": "Is carrying protection a sign of responsibility or over-preparation?",
        "answers": ["Responsible and smart", "A bit much"]
      },
      {
        "id": 43,
        "question": "Would you prefer a partner who’s experienced or one who's new to the dating scene?",
        "answers": ["Experienced is intriguing", "Newbies are adorable"]
      },
      {
        "id": 44,
        "question": "What's more appealing: a spontaneous adventure or a safe night in?",
        "answers": ["Adventure awaits", "Cozy and safe"]
      },
      {
        "id": 45,
        "question": "Do you think talking about past relationships is helpful or unnecessary?",
        "answers": ["Helpful insights", "Let’s focus on us"]
      },
      {
        "id": 46,
        "question": "How important is it for you to know your partner's health habits?",
        "answers": ["Very important", "Not a big deal"]
      },
      {
        "id": 47,
        "question": "Would you get matching tattoos with someone you're dating?",
        "answers": ["Absolutely!", "Maybe not"]
      },
      {
        "id": 48,
        "question": "Is it romantic or risky to share secrets early in a relationship?",
        "answers": ["Romantic gesture", "Better to wait"]
      },
      {
        "id": 49,
        "question": "Do you prefer to take things slow or dive right into a relationship?",
        "answers": ["Slow and steady", "Dive in headfirst"]
      }
    ]